{
	"version": 2.0,
	"questions": [
		{
			"question": "Lists in python are not mutable",
			"answers": {
				"a": "True",
				"b": "False",
				"c": "Neither true nor false",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "b",
			"difficulty": "beginner"
		},
		{
			"question": "Lists in python can be created using curly brackets",
			"answers": {
				"a": "False",
				"b": "True",
				"c": "Neither true nor false",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "a",
			"difficulty": "beginner"
		},
		{
			"question": "You can modify a tuple by converting the tuple into a list, and again convert the list back into tuple?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "False",
				"b": "True",
				"c": "Neither true nor false",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "b",
			"difficulty": "beginner"
		},
		{
			"question": "A dictionary can consist of 2 items with the same key?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "True",
				"b": "False",
				"c": "Neither true nor false",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "a",
			"difficulty": "beginner"
		},
		{
			"question": "Tuples in python are _____;  and lists are ______",
			"answers": {
				"a": "immutable, mutable",
				"b": "mutable,immutable",
				"c": "Both (a) and (b)",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "a",
			"difficulty": "intermediate"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following datatypes does not contains duplicate elements",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Set",
				"b": "List",
				"c": "Tuples",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "a",
			"difficulty": "intermediate"
		},
		{
			"question": "List indices in python always starts from ______",
			"answers": {
				"a": "1",
				"b": "0",
				"c": "-1",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "b",
			"difficulty": "intermediate"
		},
		{
			"question": "In list sort() method, the reverse parameter is mandatory ",
			"answers": {
				"a": "True",
				"b": "False",
				"c": "Cannot be determined",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "b",
			"difficulty": "intermediate"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following data types stores data in key-value format",
			"answers": {
				"a": "List",
				"b": "Set",
				"c": "Dictionaries",
				"d": "Tuples"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "c",
			"difficulty": "advanced"
		},
		{
			"question": "list.sort(reverse=’True’) will sort the list in _______ order",
			"answers": {
				"a": "Descending",
				"b": "Ascending",
				"c": "No change in the list",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "b",
			"difficulty": "advanced"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following method you would use if you wanted to add a new key-value pair to your already existing dictionary?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "append()",
				"b": "add()",
				"c": "update()",
				"d": "None of the above"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "c",
			"difficulty": "advanced"
		},
		{
			"question": "Which of the following method is used to add elements at the end of a list?",
			"answers": {
				"a": "append",
				"b": "extend",
				"c": "pop",
				"d": "reverse"
			},
			"correctAnswer": "a",
			"difficulty": "advanced"
		}
	]
}